<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>YDWC</title>
    <link>https://ydwc.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on YDWC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 16:16:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ydwc.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://ydwc.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 16:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydwc.org/about/</guid>
      <description>In the pursuit of success, people from diverse backgrounds face shared challenges. YDWC is comprised of young people from diverse backgrounds, who are often underrepresented in professional networks. Whether formal or informal, professional networks offer value to their members by providing access to knowledge, support and career opportunities. If you are from a diverse background then your parents (or grandparents) are likely to have embraced the challenge of moving to a foreign country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Insights Day 2018</title>
      <link>https://ydwc.org/events/career_insights/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Sep 2018 16:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydwc.org/events/career_insights/</guid>
      <description>Be Your Authentic Self In order to succeed professionally, graduates from diverse background need not only academic achievements but opportunities and insights from role models they can identify with. The Careers Insight dinner provides this.
For many students from diverse backgrounds, they will be amongst the first in their family or peer group to enter their chosen profession. For these students their ability to excel can be impeded by limited access to professional networks that understand the challenges of coming from a diverse background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ydwc.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydwc.org/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service</title>
      <link>https://ydwc.org/service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ydwc.org/service/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>